goodfoodeurope.com 2011-10-18

# Good Food Europe » Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy

Terms and Conditions

THESE GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE APPLY TO ALL USERS OF GOOD FOOD EUROPE.

By viewing and using the Website you will be deemed to agree to these General Terms and Conditions of Use. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms then you should stop accessing and using the Website.

**1\. Terminology:**  In these terms and conditions, the following words have the meanings set out as follows:  
“we” , “us” and “our” are a reference to Good Food Europe “you” and “your” are a reference to you.

**2\. Copyright:**  As between you and Good Food Europe the contents of the Website are good food Europe copyright. No part of the Website may be distributed, resold, published, copied, reproduced, transmitted or stored and you are not permitted to incorporate the material or any part of it in any other work or publication (whether in hard copy, electronic or any other form) without Good Food Europe’s express written consent. Good Food Europe reserves the right to prohibit links to the Website and you agree to remove or cease any link upon  Good Food Europe’s’ request. You may not frame any part of the Website by including advertising or other revenue generating material.

**3\. No Endorsements/Your Risk:**  Much of the information about products and services and reviews of products of services (“Third Party Content”) is provided by advertisers and other users on the Website and will not have been prepared by Good food Europe. Where materials have been provided by Good Food Europe these have been prepared solely for informational purposes to enable a better understanding by the users. Good Food Europe does not warrant or make any representation about anything transmitted or posted by other users via the Website or any materials it has provided for informational purposes. You further acknowledge and agree that Good Food Europe does not endorse, support, sanction, verify, encourage or agree with the Third Party Content or any user’s communications nor assume responsibility for any Third Party Content posted that is threatening, defamatory, obscene, harassing or offensive material contained therein, any infringement of third party intellectual property rights arising or any crime facilitated thereby.

The views expressed may not be the views of Good Food Europe. Good Food Europe reserves the right to remove or amend any message but is under no obligation to exercise editorial control. You acknowledge that you use and rely on the Third Party Content obtained through Good Food Europe at your own risk. You understand and agree that any material downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the Website is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any and all damages to your computer system or loss of data.

When you post an advertisement on the Website you will ensure that the information contained in the advertisement is true, accurate and correct at the time it is posted and for the period it remains on the Website. When a sale has been completed in relation to the goods or services offered in the advertisement or the information in the advertisement is no longer correct, you will correct the advertisement or notify Good Food Europe. To the extent you fail to correct the information or notify  Good Food Europe, you will indemnify us against any loss, costs, liability or damages Good Food Europe may suffer as a result of such a failure.

**4\. No Representations:**  The availability of information on the Website does not constitute a recommendation by Good Food Europe or any other person. If you enter into any transaction subsequent to accessing the Website, you do so entirely in reliance on your own judgement and inquiries and not in reliance on any statements, warranties or representations made to you or to any other person by or on behalf of Good Food Europe.

**5\. Buying:**  When you buy an item on the Website you will ensure that the information you provide to the seller is accurate, correct and that you have all the necessary rights to buy that item. You agree that where you reach an agreement to buy an item from another user or advertiser you will complete that transaction and provide payment for that item in accordance with the terms agreed with the relevant seller and Good Food Europe will not be liable for any transaction you conclude or advertisements you pursue.

**6.Termination:**  Good Food Europe, May:

* terminate your access and registration as a user to any part of, or all of, the Website with or without cause, with or without notice effective immediately, for any reason whatsoever (including without limitation, a failure by you to comply with any of the General Terms and Conditions of Use);  
* at any time and without notice, remove, amend and/or vary any of the content which appears on the Website or cease operating the Website in whole or in part.

**7\. Privacy and Personal Information:**  Please refer to the Privacy Statement [for further conditions relating to your personal information (the terms of such Privacy Statement are incorporated into these General Terms and Conditions of Use).

**8\. Links and Advertising:**  The Website may include links to other websites not owned by Good Food Europe and/or advertising not related to Good Food Europe. If you visit a linked website or contact an advertiser, that dealing will be solely between you and that other website or advertiser at your own risk. These links do not imply Good Food Europe’s  endorsement of that other website or product or service being advertised (as applicable) or any association with their operators unless this is specifically stated on the Website.

You will not misuse your ability to share or to access information provided in the classifieds section of the website and Good Food Europe is not responsible in any way for your use of, or access to, the information contained in the classified section.

**9\. Liability:**  To the fullest extent permitted by law, Good Food Europe excludes all responsibility and liability in relation to the Website and Good Food Europe will not be responsible for errors or misstatements or be liable whether in contract, tort (including negligence) or otherwise for any loss or damage however caused (whether direct, indirect, consequential, special or loss of profits). Where any such liability cannot be excluded Good Food Europe limits it to the smallest permissible amount.

**10\. Registration:**  In order to use an Information Sharing Function you are required to become a registered user and will be required to adhere to additional terms and conditions for registered users. You must complete the registration process by providing Good Food Europe with current, complete and accurate information as prompted by the relevant registration form. Good  Food Europe reserves the right to reject any application for registration.

**11\. Changes to Terms of Use:**  Good Food Europe reserves the right to change these terms and conditions of use at any time by notifying users of the existence of revised terms and conditions through the Website. By continuing to access the Website, you agree to be bound by the amended terms and conditions. You should check from time to time to see if these terms have changed or not.

**12\. Law:**  These terms and conditions are governed by and will be construed in accordance with the laws of Great Britain and you submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of Great Britain.

**13.Contact:**  If you have any questions or concerns in relation to the Website or these General Terms and Conditions of Use please contact us by

## Privacy Policy

Good Food Europe strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

##### HOW WE GATHER INFORMATION FROM USERS

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities isn’t  which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. Like most Web sites, Good Food Europe also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

##### WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Good Food Europe to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by Good Food Europe and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Good Food Europe may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

##### AFFILIATED SITES, LINKED SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS

Good Food Europe expects is partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Good Food Europe page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Good Food Europe you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Good Food Europeis not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Good Food Europe does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Good Food Europe and this policy.

##### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Good Food Europe reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

##### GOVERNING LAW

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Great Britain If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Great Britain.
